

CONTACT ME

- +48 791 574 676
- □ www..com
- T. Szewczenki 37 51-352 Wrocław

EDUCATION

TOURISM AND RECREATION

Academy of Physical Education in Wrocław

2011 - 2014

SKILLS

- UI/UX
- HTML
- CSS
- Sass
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- Photoshop
- VSC
- WordPress

Kacper Sapis Fronted Developer

PROFILE

My name is Kacper Sapis. I am a young creative person who builds my experience by running my own business and I received training many courses to improve my personal development. I am not afraid of what is new and I am happy to take up new challenges. I treat each day as an opportunity to broaden my competences and horizons.

I am interested in innovative solutions, automation of processes taking place in the company, data analysis and modern forms of business.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business owner

2016 - 2023

Travel Agency PIKADA I pikada.net

For almost four years I have my own business in which I focus mainly on e-marketing, website positioning, Facebook Ads campaigns, I have been running my own business for almost four years now. I mainly focus on e-marketing, website positioning, Facebook Ad campaigns and fan page mangement, e-mail marketing and creating landing pages. I also design and produce leaflets, posters and catalogs.

Web developer 2020 -

Znajdebusa I znajdebusa.pl

As a webdeveloper, I have created and co-own a website and a webservice. I have personally contributed to coming up with the idea and to the writing of the code. I am responsible for promoting the website and acquiring new clients through social media and e-mail marketing. I have designed the graphics for the website and the leaflets.

Web developer Intern

2019 - 2020

IMADO I imado.co/pl/

As an intern, I have participated in designing and creating graphics for websites and attracting new customers. I have also participated in creating Facebook Ads and Google Ads campaigns.

REFERENCES

Damian Bartnik

IMADO

Phone: +48 792 030 711 **Email:** info@imado.pl